Mauli Karande

Java Developer

Personal Info

Address

Hadapsar, Pune

Phone

(+91) 7378938893

E-mail

maulikarande2001@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Date of birth 21 April 2000 Java Developer with 2 years of experience in application development designed for client-server environment. Have good knowledge of OOPS concept, Collection framework, Multithreading, Java8 and Spring Boot. Worked on Restful Web Services. Known as a genuine team player. Adapt easily and quickly to new work environments.

Experience

Software Engineer

Avocado Systems, Pune

(Jan 2022 - Feb 2023)

- Worked on various reports and Dashboard, transferring those from MySQL to Elastic Search queries using Elastic Search Java Spring Boot Framework.
- Wrote java rest client to generate dummy data.
- Wrote Docker file and YAML file for Deployment, also wrote shell scripts.

Java Developer

IP Tech System, Pune

(May 2021 - Dec 2021)

- Involved in Estimation, Planning, Design, Development.
- Responsible for coding, unit testing and defect fixing of web application
- Actively involved in troubleshooting defects raised in both the releases.

Key Skills

Core Java Elastic search, MYSQL, H2

OOPS concept's Spring Boot

Exception Handling Spring Security

Multithreading REST API

Collection Framework Docker, Kubernetes

Java8 Shell Script

JDBC Template Linux(Ubuntu16, Centos7, RHEL7)

JPA JIRA, GIT

HTML, CSS, JAVA Script

Education

New Arts, Commerce & Science college of Ahmed Nagar.

BSC Computer Science

April 2019 - April 2021